cbolobank.com 2015-03-23

# Visit:

A-16185                                                                                           Rev. July 2014           PAGE 1
    FACTS           WHAT DOES CENTRAL BANCOMPANY DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
                    Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers
     Why?           the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share,
                    and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
                    The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                    have with us. This information can include:
     What?                 Social Security number and income
                           account balances and payment history
                           credit history and transaction history
                    All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.
     How?           In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal
                    information; the reasons Central Bancompany chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
 Reasons we can share personal information                                                Does Central           Can you limit
                                                                                      Bancompany share?          this sharing?
 For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your
 transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                      Yes                    No
 investigations, or report to credit bureaus
 For our marketing purposes - to offer our products and services to you                         Yes                    No
 For joint marketing with other financial companies                                             Yes                    No
 For our affiliates everyday business purposes -
                                                                                                Yes                    No
 information about your transactions and experiences
 For our affiliates everyday business purposes -
                                                                                                Yes                   Yes
 information about your creditworthiness
 For our affiliates to market to you                                                            Yes                   Yes
 For our nonaffiliates to market to you                                                         No              We don’t share
                     Detach and mail the form below to the address listed.
     To limit        Please note:
        our          If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice.
     sharing         When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
                     However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
   Questions?       Visit: www.cbolobank.com and click “Contact Us”
Detach and mail form below to:
Central Bank of Lake of the Ozarks
Attn: Customer Service
PO Box 207
Osage Beach, MO 65065
 Mail-in Form
 If you have a joint         Mark any/all you want to limit:
 account, your                    Do not share information about my creditworthiness with your affiliate for
 choice(s) will apply             their everyday business purposes.
 to everyone on your              Do not allow your affiliates to use my personal information to market to me.
 account unless
 you mark below.            Name
       Apply my             Address
       choices only
       to me.               City, State, Zip
                            Last 4 digits of SSN

Who we are
Who is providing this notice?      Central Bancompany and its affiliates (please see below for List of Affiliates)
What we do
How does Central Bancompany To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use
protect my personal information? security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include
                                   computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does Central Bancompany We collect your personal information, for example, when you
collect my personal information?      open an account or deposit money
                                      pay your bills or apply for a loan
                                      use your credit or debit card
                                   We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus,
                                   affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?     Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                      sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes -
                                        information about your creditworthiness
                                      affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                      sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                   State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit          Your choices will apply to everyone on your account unless you
sharing for an account I hold      advise us otherwise.
jointly with someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                         Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                      Our affiliates include companies who are members of Central Bancompany;
                                        financial companies such as trust, credit card and insurance.
Nonaffiliates                      Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                      Central Bancompany does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing                    A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together
                                   market financial products or services to you.
                                      Our joint marketing partners include companies that provide marketing services
                                   on our behalf and other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements.
List of Affiliates
Boone County National Bank                Central Trust & Investment Company                  InvestorServices
Central Bank                              Central Mortgage Company                            Jefferson Bank of Missouri
Central Bank of Audrain County            City Bank                                           ONB Bank & Trust Company
Central Bank of Lake of the Ozarks        Dogwood Insurance Agency, L.L.C.                    Third National Bank
Central Bank of St. Louis                 Empire Bank                                         Ozark Mountain Bank
Central Bank of the Midwest               First Central Bank
